{
  "questions" : [
    "{"question":"She ... my friend !" , "answers":["are","were ","is ","will"], "correctIndex":2 },"
"{"question":"I ... a translator ." , "answers":["is","am","are","has"], "correctIndex":1 },"
"{"question":"She ... my friend !" , "answers":["are","were ","is ","will"], "correctIndex":2 },"
"{"question":"I ... a translator ." , "answers":["is","am","are","has"], "correctIndex":1 },"
"{"question":"She ... my friend !" , "answers":["are","were ","is ","will"], "correctIndex":2 },"
"{"question":"I ... a translator ." , "answers":["is","am","are","has"], "correctIndex":1 },"
"{"question":"She ... my friend !" , "answers":["are","were ","is ","will"], "correctIndex":2 },"
"{"question":"I ... a translator ." , "answers":["is","am","are","has"], "correctIndex":1 },"
"{"question":"She ... my friend !" , "answers":["are","were ","is ","will"], "correctIndex":2 },"
"{"question":"I ... a translator ." , "answers":["is","am","are","has"], "correctIndex":1 },"

  ]
}
